<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="category_items">
        <item>Tops</item>
        <item>Bottoms</item>
        <item>Outerwear</item>
        <item>Shoes</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="material_items">
        <item>Cotton</item>
        <item>Leather</item>
        <item>Polyester</item>
        <item>Wool</item>
        <item>Nylon</item>
        <item>Acrylic</item>
        <item>Rubber</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="season_items">
        <item>Spring</item>
        <item>Summer</item>
        <item>Fall</item>
        <item>Winter</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="purchase_items">
        <item>Brand new</item>
        <item>Thrifted</item>
        <item>Second-hand online</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="tips_headings">
        <item>What is fast fashion?</item>
        <item>What is slow fashion?</item>
        <item>What is a capsule wardrobe?</item>
        <item>What should I think about before making a purchase?</item>
        <item>What should I do with clothes I don\'t wear anymore?</item>
        <item>What fabrics should I look for?</item>
        <item>Where should I shop from?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="tips_content">
        <item>Fast fashion can be defined as cheap,
            trendy clothing that samples ideas from the catwalk or
            celebrity culture and turns them into garments in
            high street stores at breakneck speed to meet consumer demand.
            The idea is to get the newest styles on the market as fast as possible,
            so shoppers can snap them up while they are still at the height of
            their popularity and then, sadly, discard them after a few wears.
            It plays into the idea that outfit repeating is a fashion faux pas and
            that if you want to stay relevant, you have to sport the latest looks as
            they happen. It forms a key part of the toxic system of overproduction
            and consumption that has made fashion one of the world’s largest polluters. [Source: Good on You]</item>
        <item>Essentially, slow fashion is thinking before you buy clothes.
            Not just thinking about whether you really need that tempting
            mainstream shirt posing behind the counter of some well-known clothing
            brand\'s store or not, but thinking about where the garments come from
            and being aware of how they are created. It is a new eco-friendly approach to
            fashion that focuses on sustainability, recycling, or acquiring second-hand
            clothes and encourages the idea of buying better quality garments
            that will last longer, making sure that their manufacturing processes
            have been fair and ethical to people, animals and the environment in general. [Source: The Eco Hub]</item>
        <item>A capsule wardrobe is a limited selection of interchangeable clothing pieces
            that complement each other. These are often classic pieces that do not
            go out of style and are primarily composed of neutral colors. A capsule
            wardrobe allows you to create a variety of different outfits with a small
            selection of clothes. [Source: Sustainably Chic]</item>
        <item>Here are 7 questions to ask before you purchase a new clothing item:\n
        <b>1. Where will I wear it?\n
        2. Can I think of at least 5 outfits to wear it with?\n
        3. Is it easy to wash?\n
        4. Is it comfortable?\n
        5. Would I still want it if it wasn\'t on sale?\n
        6. Does it fit my body right now?\n
            7. Is it too trendy?</b></item>
        <item>The average American throws away 81 pounds of clothing each year.
            Unfortunately, it takes years and decades for most fabrics to break down.
            Natural materials like cotton, linen, hemp, and silk can biodegrade pretty quickly in the right conditions,
            from a couple weeks to around half a year. Wool and bamboo take longer, often decomposing in 1-5 years.
            Synthetic fabrics (which is what most conventional clothes are made of, like polyester)
            can take anywhere from 20-200 years to break down!\n\n
            It\'s a common misconception that you need to get rid of all your fast
            fashion when you begin your sustainable fashion journey.
            If you like certain fast fashion pieces and wear them regularly, keep them.
            Sustainable fashion isn’t really about what brands are in your wardrobe.
            It\'s more about your mindset and habits. A person who buys fast fashion,
            but only buys what they need and makes their clothes last a long time,
            is way more sustainable than a person who buys excessively from sustainable brands. [Source: Imperfect Idealist]\n\n
            If there are items that you haven\'t worn in over 1-2 years, you can consider:\n
            <b>1. Repurpose clothes in poor condition.</b> For example, you can use old, holey socks as cleaning rags.\n
            <b>2. Bring nicer items to a consignment shop.</b>\n
            <b>3. Sell your clothes online.</b> Try posting your clothing on platforms like
            Depop, Poshmark, or Facebook Marketplace.\n
            <b>4. Compost clothes made from natural fibers.</b>\n
            <b>5. Donate them to charity or thrift stores.</b>
            Why is donating your clothes low on the list?
            Sadly, only 20% of clothes donated to thrift stores
            is actually sold—the rest is trashed or sold to developing countries,
            where it puts local textile workers out of jobs. If you can get rid
            of your clothing through one of the earlier methods,
            it’s more likely to actually stay out of the trash.
        </item>
        <item>
            Generally, natural fabrics like organic cotton and linen (made from plants) and Tencel (made from sustainable wood pulp)
            are more sustainable than man-made fabrics like Polyester and Nylon.\n
            Sustainable fabrics:\n
            <b>Organic cotton</b>\n
            <b>Hemp</b>\n
            <b>Linen</b>\n
            <b>Silk</b>\n
            <b>Wool</b>\n
            <b>Lenzing Tencel</b>\n\n
            <b>Unsustainable fabrics to avoid:</b>\n
            <b>Polyester.</b>
            This is short for any fabric made from a synthetic, man-made polymer,
            which means polyester is essentially plastic.\n
            <b>Nylon.</b> Nylon is a silky thermoplastic,
            often made from fossil fuels, that can be melted and
            turned into fabric fibres.\n
            <b>Acrylic.</b> This is a fabric made from plastic
            threads created through the use of fossil fuels like petroleum.\n
            <b>Cotton.</b> This is a natural fibre that causes problems
            due to high water consumption, high levels of pesticides and pollution when overfarmed.\n
            <b>Rayon.</b> This is a fibre that comes from natural wood pulp
            but requires harmful chemicals to convert it to cellulose,
            and can also be dangerous to wear. [Source: FutureLearn]\n
        </item>
        <item>
            Thrift stores, second-hand platforms, sustainable brands.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="material_graph_colours">
        <item>@color/third</item>
        <item>@color/graph_1_teal</item>
        <item>@color/graph_2_light_teal</item>
        <item>@color/graph_3_green</item>
        <item>@color/graph_4_lime</item>
        <item>@color/graph_5_ochre</item>
        <item>@color/graph_6_orange</item>
    </integer-array>
    <integer-array name="purchase_loc_graph_colours">
        <item>@color/second</item>
        <item>@color/graph_4_lime</item>
        <item>@color/graph_6_orange</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>